Register of the John Davis Lodge papers, 1886-1987
Hoover Institution Archives
- Ambassador to Argentina (1969-1974) File, 1966-1975 (Boxes 186-213)
  - Office file, 1969-1973, undated
    - Travel file
      - 1969
        - Panama (Box-folder 205: 7)
        - USS Brazil (Box-folder 205: 8)
      - 1970
        - Argentina (Box-folder 205: 9)
        - Mar del Plata (Box-folder 205: 10)
        - Spain (Box-folder 205: 11)
      - 1971
        - Antartica (Box-folder 205: 12)
        - Copahue (Box-folder 205: 13)
        - Europe and the United States (Box-folder 205: 14)
        - Panama (Box-folder 205: 15)
        - Pinamar (Box-folder 206: 1)
        - United States (Box-folder 206: 2)
      - 1972
        - Bogota (Box-folder 206: 3)
        - Europe and the United States (Box-folder 206: 4)
        - Formosa (Box-folder 206: 5)
        - Nice, Cannes, Ibiza, and Madrid (Box-folder 206: 6)
        - UNITAS and Santiago (Box-folder 206: 7)
        - United Hispanic-American Parade, New York (Box-folder 206: 8)
      - 1973
        - Copahue (Box-folder 206: 9)
        - Europe (Box-folder 206: 10)
        - Pinamar (Box-folder 206: 11)
        - United States (Box-folder 206: 12-13)
        - Washington, D.C. (Box-folder 206: 14)
      - Travel vouchers (Box-folder 206: 15)
  - Speeches and writings, 1969-1974
    - 1969 (Box-folder 206: 16-18, 207: 1-3)
    - 1970 (Box-folder 207: 4-11)
    - 1971 (Box-folder 208: 1-7)
    - 1972 (Box-folder 208: 8)
    - Notes, 1973 (Box-folder 208: 9)
    - 1974 (Box-folder 208: 10, 209: 1-2)
  - Subject file, circa 1969-1974, undated
    - Agnew, Spiro (Box-folder 209: 3)
    - American Foreign Service Association (Box-folder 209: 4)
    - Anti-Americanism (Box-folder 209: 5)
    - Anti-communism (Box-folder 209: 6)
    - Argentina
      - General (Box-folder 209: 7-8)
      - Economic conditions (Box-folder 209: 9)
      - History (Box-folder 209: 10)
      - Miscellany (Box-folder 209: 11)
      - Politics and government (Box-folder 209: 12)
      - Population (Box-folder 209: 13)
    - Black Panthers (Box-folder 209: 14)
    - Buenos Aires (Box-folder 209: 15)
    - Bulgaria (Box-folder 209: 16)
      Printed declaration of Simeon II, King of the Bulgarians.
    - Burke, Edmund (Box-folder 209: 17)
    - Connecticut (Box-folder 209: 18)
    - Council Against Communist Aggression and Alexis de Tocqueville Society (Box-folder 209: 19)
    - Council for Latin America (Box-folder 210: 1)
    - Diplomatic and Consular Officers, Retired (DACOR) (Box-folder 210: 2)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Box-folder 210: 3)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation (F.B.I.) (Box-folder 210: 4)
    - Foreign Policy Research Institute, University of Pennsylvania (Box-folder 210: 5)
    - France, Navy (Box-folder 210: 6)
    - Frelinghuysen, Peter (Box-folder 210: 7-9)
    - Hearst, William R., Jr. (Box-folder 210: 10)
    - Inter-American Bar Association (Box-folder 210: 11)
    - International relations (Box-folder 210: 12)
    - Javits, Benjamin (Box-folder 210: 13)
    - Kennan, George (Box-folder 210: 14)
    - Latin America (Box-folder 210: 15)
    - Library of Congress (Box-folder 210: 16)
    - Lodge, George C. (Box-folder 211: 1)
    - Lodge, Henry Cabot (Box-folder 211: 2)
    - Mather, George (Box-folder 211: 3)
    - Middle East (Box-folder 211: 4)
    - Miscellany (Box-folder 211: 5-6)
    - Mitrione, Dan (Box-folder 211: 7)
      Eulogy by John Lodge.
    - Morison, Samuel Eliot (Box-folder 211: 8)
    - Morris, Robert (Box-folder 211: 9)
    - National Petroleum Corporation, Inc. (Box-folder 211: 10)
    - Nixon, Richard M. (Box-folder 211: 11-12, 212: 1)
    - Northwood Institute (Box-folder 212: 2)
    - Pan American Society of the United States (Box-folder 212: 3)
    - Pasquaney (Box-folder 212: 4)
    - Peron, Juan (Box-folder 212: 5)
    - Rentschler, William H. (Box-folder 212: 6)
    - Rockford College (Box-folder 212: 7)
    - Sonnenberg, Ben (Box-folder 212: 8)
    - Spain
      - General (Box-folder 212: 9-10)
      - Documentary film (Box-folder 212: 11)
    - Taxpayers Committee to End Foreign Aid (Box-folder 213: 1)
    - Terrorism (Box-folder 213: 2)
    - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics (U.S.S.R.) (Box-folder 213: 3)
    - United States
      - Defense (Box-folder 213: 4)
      - Economic conditions (Box-folder 213: 5)
      - Foreign aid (Box-folder 213: 6)
      - Foreign relations
        - General (Box-folder 213: 7)
        - Argentina (Box-folder 213: 8)
        - Latin America (Box-folder 213: 9)
        - Spain (Box-folder 213: 10)
        - U.S.S.R. (Box-folder 213: 11)
      - Politics and government (Box-folder 213: 12)
    - Vietnam (Box-folder 213: 13)
    - Watergate (Box-folder 213: 14)
    - Wharton, Edith (Box-folder 213: 15)
- Interim Years (1974-1983) File, 1973-1983 (Boxes 213-259)
  Biographical material, correspondence, speeches and writings, and general subject material.
  - Biographical file, 1975-1983, undated
    - Address lists, calling cards, resumes (Box-folder 213: 16)
    - Awards (Box-folder 213: 17)
    - Biographical sketches (Box-folder 213: 18)
    - Church memberships (Box-folder 213: 19)
    - Clippings, 1975-1982, undated (Box-folder 213: 20-23, 214: 1-5)
    - Daily schedules (Box-folder 214: 6-8)
    - Family
      - General (Box-folder 214: 9)
      - Davis, Charles Henry (Box-folder 214: 10)
      - Griswold family (Box-folder 214: 11-12)
      - Oyarazabal, Antonio de (Box-folder 215: 1)
    - Honorary degrees (Box-folder 215: 2)
    - Memberships
      - General (Box-folder 215: 3)
      - Alumni associations (Box-folder 215: 4-8)
        Includes Harvard University, Middlesex School, and St. Albans School.
      - Army and Navy Club (Box-folder 215: 9)
      - Chowder and Marching Club (Box-folder 215: 10, 216: 1)
      - Dutch Treat Club (Box-folder 216: 2)
      - Explorer's Club (Box-folder 216: 3)
      - Fox Club (Box-folder 216: 4)
      - National Wildlife Federation (Box-folder 216: 5)
    - Oral history, Columbia University (Box-folder 216: 6)
    - Social functions
      - 1975 (Box-folder 216: 7-8)
      - 1976 (Box-folder 216: 9, 217: 1)
      - 1977 (Box-folder 217: 2-3)
      - 1978 (Box-folder 217: 4-5)
      - 1979 (Box-folder 217: 6-7)
      - 1980 (Box-folder 217: 8-9, 218: 1-2)
      - 1981 (Box-folder 218: 3-4)
      - 1982 (Box-folder 218: 5-6)
      - 1983 (Box-folder 218: 7)
    - Travel file - trip to China and the Far East, 1981 (Box-folder 219: 1-2)
      Includes correspondence with Warren Burger.
  - Correspondence, 1973-1983
    - General
      - 1975 (Box-folder 219: 3-6)
      - 1976 (Box-folder 219: 7-9)
      - 1977 (Box-folder 219: 10-11, 220: 1-2)
      - 1978 (Box-folder 220: 3-4)
      - 1979 (Box-folder 220: 5-7)
      - 1980 (Box-folder 220: 8-11)
      - 1981 (Box-folder 220: 12-15)
      - 1982 (Box-folder 220: 16, 221: 1-2)
      - 1983 (Box-folder 221: 3)
    - Accion Revolucionaria Anticomunista, 1977 (Box-folder 221: 4)
    - Aherne, Mr. and Mrs. Brian, undated (Box-folder 221: 5)
    - Ainley, Mrs. E. C., 1974 (Box-folder 221: 6)
    - Alba, Jaime, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 221: 7)
    - Alcorn, Hugh Meade, Jr., 1977 (Box-folder 221: 8)
    - Alcorta, Gloria, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 221: 9)
    - Aldrich, Richard, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 221: 10)
    - Allen, Richard J., 1977 (Box-folder 221: 11)
    - Allen, Richard V., 1980-1981 (Box-folder 221: 12)
    - Allen, Walter C., 1975 (Box-folder 221: 13)
    - Alliance Francaise of Fairfield County, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 221: 14)
    - Alsop, John, 1974-1983 (Box-folder 221: 15)
    - American-Chilean Council, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 221: 16-17)
      Includes correspondence with Marvin Liebman.
    - American Flag Institute, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 221: 18)
    - American Legion Post, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 221: 19)
    - American Society of the French Legion of Honor, 1983 (Box-folder 222: 1)
    - Americans for Change, 1980 (Box-folder 222: 2)
    - Anderson, George W., 1979 (Box-folder 222: 3)
    - Annenberg, Leonore, 1981 (Box-folder 222: 4)
    - Annenberg, Walter, 1975-1982 (Box-folder 222: 5)
    - Araoz, Carmen, undated (Box-folder 222: 6)
    - Arguelles, Ramon, 1975 (Box-folder 222: 7)
    - Armstrong, Edward, 1977 (Box-folder 222: 8)
    - Associated Clubs, 1981 (Box-folder 222: 9)
    - Association of Former Intelligence Officers, 1979 (Box-folder 222: 10)
    - Atlantic Council of the United States, 1977 (Box-folder 222: 11)
    - Attwood, William, 1979 (Box-folder 222: 12)
    - Auchincloss, Hugh, undated (Box-folder 222: 13)
    - Babcock, Catherine, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 222: 14)
    - Baird, Jack, 1973 (Box-folder 222: 15)
    - Baker, Howard, 1980 (Box-folder 222: 16)
    - Baker, James A., III, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 222: 17)
    - Baldrige, Letitia, 1983 (Box-folder 222: 18)
    - Baldrige, Malcolm, 1981 (Box-folder 222: 19)
    - Baldwin, Herbert, 1979 (Box-folder 222: 20)
    - Baldwin, Raymond E., 1982 (Box-folder 222: 21)
    - Barall, Milton, 1974-1983 (Box-folder 222: 22)
    - Basso, Adolfo, 1977 (Box-folder 222: 23)
    - Batuz, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 222: 24)
    - Bernini, Federico, 1976 (Box-folder 222: 25)
    - Black, Shirley Temple, 1976 (Box-folder 222: 26)
    - Bliss, Robert, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 222: 27)
    - Bobich, Gica, 1974-1982 (Box-folder 222: 28)
    - Bobrinskoy, Nicholas A., 1974-1983 (Box-folder 222: 29)
    - Bodisco, Aino de, 1974-1983 (Box-folder 222: 30)
    - Bohlen, Charles, undated (Box-folder 222: 31)
    - Bolton, Frances, 1975 (Box-folder 222: 32)
    - Bowden, Dina, 1975 (Box-folder 222: 33)
    - Braden, Spruille, 1977 (Box-folder 222: 34)
    - Bradley, Kenneth, 1978 (Box-folder 222: 35)
    - Braga, George, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 222: 36)
    - Braggiotti, D. Chadwick, 1977-1983 (Box-folder 222: 37)
    - Braggiotti, Mario, 1983 (Box-folder 223: 1)
    - Braggiotti, Tobar, 1975 (Box-folder 223: 2)
    - Brett, Homer, 1977-1983 (Box-folder 223: 3)
    - Brooks, B. V., Jr., 1974-1975 (Box-folder 223: 4)
    - Browne, Ken, 1974 (Box-folder 223: 5)
    - Brownell, Herbert, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 223: 6)
    - Buchanan, Patrick, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 223: 7)
    - Buckley, James, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 223: 8)
    - Buckley, William F., Jr., 1974-1983 (Box-folder 223: 9-11)
    - Bullock, Hugh, 1974 (Box-folder 223: 12)
    - Burger, Warren, 1983 (Box-folder 223: 13)
    - Bush, Dorothy, undated (Box-folder 223: 14)
    - Bush, George, 1975-1981 (Box-folder 223: 15)
    - Bush, Prescott, Sr., 1980 (Box-folder 223: 16)
    - Butash, Adrian, 1978 (Box-folder 223: 17)
    - Capitol Hill Club, 1975 (Box-folder 223: 18)
    - Capitol Hill Foundation, 1973 (Box-folder 223: 19)
    - Carcano, Miguel Angel, 1973 (Box-folder 223: 20)
    - Carey, Charles, 1974-1981 (Box-folder 223: 21)
    - Carroll-Abbing, J. Patrick, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 223: 22)
    - Carter, James (Jimmy), 1976 (Box-folder 223: 23)
    - Case, Clifford, 1982 (Box-folder 223: 24)
    - Casey, William, 1980 (Box-folder 223: 25)
    - Castro, Raul, 1978 (Box-folder 223: 26)
    - Cefaratti, Anthony J., 1973 (Box-folder 223: 27)
    - Center for Inter-American Relations, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 223: 28)
    - Cerlanek, Frank, 1975 (Box-folder 223: 29)
    - Chapuis, Jane, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 223: 30)
    - Chase, Allen C., 1977 (Box-folder 223: 31)
    - Cholmeley-Jones, E. O. Nigel, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 224: 1)
    - Cinelli, Veronica, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 224: 2)
    - Citizens' Legal Defense Fund, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 224: 3)
    - Clark, Pat, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 224: 4)
    - Clark, William P., 1982 (Box-folder 224: 5)
    - Clemens, Cyril, 1967-1977 (Box-folder 224: 6)
    - Clifford, Arthur, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 224: 7)
    - Cohn, Roy, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 224: 8)
    - Colby, William, 1975 (Box-folder 224: 9)
    - Cole, Albert, 1976 (Box-folder 224: 10)
    - Conant, Luther, 1974 (Box-folder 224: 11)
    - Connecticut Center for Continuing Education, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 224: 12)
    - Connecticut Humane Society, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 224: 13)
    - Connecticut Political Action Committee, 1981 (Box-folder 224: 14)
    - Connecticut Republican Labor League, 1974 (Box-folder 224: 15)
    - Conner, Leonard, 1979 (Box-folder 224: 16)
    - Cospito, Rene, 1974-1982 (Box-folder 224: 17)
    - Cotton, Helen, 1974-1981 (Box-folder 224: 18)
    - Council of Former Governors, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 224: 19)
    - Cowles, Gardner, 1983 (Box-folder 224: 20)
    - Cramer, Robert, 1976 (Box-folder 224: 21)
    - Crane, Philip, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 224: 22)
    - Crocker, Edward, 1979 (Box-folder 224: 23)
    - Cronan, Carey, 1974 (Box-folder 224: 24)
    - Cupelli, Alberto, 1976 (Box-folder 224: 25)
    - Curry, Donald, 1983 (Box-folder 224: 26)
    - Curtis, Carl T., 1973-1975 (Box-folder 224: 27)
    - Cushman, Charles, 1974-1981 (Box-folder 224: 28)
    - Dambrava, Vytautas, 1974 (Box-folder 224: 29)
    - Davis, Fitzroy, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 224: 30)
    - Davis, Glenn, 1974-1982 (Box-folder 224: 31)
    - Davis, Shelby Cullom, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 224: 32)
    - DeForest, Jack, 1983 (Box-folder 224: 33)
    - DeLong, Edmund, 1974 (Box-folder 224: 34)
    - DeMille, Evelyn, 1974 (Box-folder 224: 35)
    - DeNardis, Lawrence, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 224: 36)
    - Devlin, Harry, 1980 (Box-folder 225: 1)
    - Dewart, Thomas, 1974-1981 (Box-folder 225: 2)
    - DeWitt, John, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 225: 3)
    - Dohanos, Stephen, 1979 (Box-folder 225: 4)
    - Donahue, Edward, 1980 (Box-folder 225: 5)
    - Driscoll, Alfred, 1975 (Box-folder 225: 6)
    - Dudley, Henry, 1974-1982 (Box-folder 225: 7)
    - Duke, Angier Biddle, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 225: 8)
    - Eames, Emma, 1980 (Box-folder 225: 9)
    - Eames, Hamilton, 1975-1981 (Box-folder 225: 10)
    - Eason, Myles, 1974 (Box-folder 225: 11)
    - Eisenhower, Barbara, 1980 (Box-folder 225: 12)
    - Ellinger, John, 1974-1983 (Box-folder 225: 13)
    - Ellsworth, Robert, 1980 (Box-folder 225: 14)
    - Eppes, William, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 225: 15)
    - Erize, Jeannette, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 225: 16)
    - Espil, Jorge, 1977 (Box-folder 225: 17)
    - Etting, Mr. and Mrs. Emlen, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 225: 18)
    - Faris, Mrs. Barry, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 225: 19)
    - Farley, Mrs. James, 1981 (Box-folder 225: 20)
    - Field, David J., 1981 (Box-folder 225: 21)
    - Filosa, Gary, II, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 225: 22)
    - Fish, Hamilton, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 225: 23)
    - Fitzpatrick, John, 1976 (Box-folder 225: 24)
    - Folger, Mrs. John C., 1981 (Box-folder 225: 25)
    - Ford, George, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 225: 26)
    - Ford, Gerald, 1981 (Box-folder 225: 27)
    - Former Members of Congress, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 225: 28)
    - Foundation for Economic Education, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 225: 29)
    - Fraleigh, William N., 1975-1982 (Box-folder 225: 30)
    - Francoeur, Philip, 1981 (Box-folder 225: 31)
    - Frost, Jack, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 225: 32)
    - Galvez, Jose Ivan, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 226: 1)
    - Garrigues, Antonio, 1975-1983 (Box-folder 226: 2)
    - Gates, Thomas S., 1983 (Box-folder 226: 3)
    - Gaussen, Gerard, 1976 (Box-folder 226: 4)
    - Gerard, James, 1982 (Box-folder 226: 5)
    - Gerety, Pierce, 1982 (Box-folder 226: 6)
    - Gilman, Lawrence, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 226: 7)
    - Gimbel, Bernard, 1975 (Box-folder 226: 8)
    - Gingles, Robert, 1974 (Box-folder 226: 9)
    - Goldwater, Barry, 1974 (Box-folder 226: 10)
    - Graeber, George, 1980 (Box-folder 226: 11)
    - Grandville, Comte Jean de la Chevardiere de la, 1981 (Box-folder 226: 12)
    - Granville, W. Irving, 1979 (Box-folder 226: 13)
    - Grasso, Ella, 1975-1982 (Box-folder 226: 14)
    - Griswold, Rita C., 1974 (Box-folder 226: 15)
    - Guest, Winston, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 226: 16)
    - Haedo, Elsie, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 226: 17)
    - Haig, Alexander, 1974-1982 (Box-folder 226: 18)
    - Hall, Leonard W., 1979 (Box-folder 226: 19)
    - Hamilton, Natalie Wales, 1975-1981 (Box-folder 226: 20)
    - Hansen, George, 1977 (Box-folder 226: 21)
    - Haring, John, 1975 (Box-folder 226: 22)
    - Harlow, Arthur B., 1977-1983 (Box-folder 226: 23)
    - Harlow, Bryce, 1974 (Box-folder 226: 24)
    - Hartford Courant, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 226: 25)
    - Hartmann, Robert, 1975 (Box-folder 226: 26)
    - Harvard University, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 226: 27)
    - Hatch, Orrin, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 226: 28)
    - Hearst, William Randolph, Jr., 1974 (Box-folder 226: 29)
    - Helms, Jesse, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 226: 30)
    - Hepburn, Katharine, 1976 (Box-folder 226: 31)
    - Heritage Foundation, 1983 (Box-folder 226: 32)
    - Hickling, R. Anderson, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 226: 33)
    - Higham, Charles, 1976 (Box-folder 226: 34)
    - Hill, Robert, 1973-1983 (Box-folder 226: 35)
    - Hillings, Patrick, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 226: 36)
    - Hilson, Edwin, 1977 (Box-folder 226: 37)
    - Hilson, John, 1974 (Box-folder 226: 38)
    - Hinman, George, 1975 (Box-folder 226: 39)
    - Hirsch, Herbert, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 226: 40)
    - Hobart and William Smith Colleges, 1982 (Box-folder 226: 41)
    - Hoppe, Henry R., 1975 (Box-folder 226: 42)
    - Hotchkis, Preston, 1981 (Box-folder 226: 43)
    - Houghton, Laura, 1981 (Box-folder 226: 44)
    - Humphrey, Hubert H., 1976-1978 (Box-folder 226: 45)
    - Institute for the Study of Diplomacy, 1981 (Box-folder 226: 46)
    - Inter-American Bar Association, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 226: 47)
    - Ireland, Mr. and Mrs. Livingston, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 227: 1)
    - Iribarne, M. F., 1975 (Box-folder 227: 2)
    - Irwin, John N., II, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 227: 3)
    - Italian Alliance Clubs, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 227: 4)
    - Ives, Colin, 1975 (Box-folder 227: 5)
    - Jackson, Don, undated (Box-folder 227: 6)
    - James, E. Pendleton, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 227: 7)
    - Janis, Martin, 1981 (Box-folder 227: 8)
    - Javits, Jacob, 1974-1983 (Box-folder 227: 9)
    - Johnson, George B., 1979-1980 (Box-folder 227: 10)
    - Jones, Jerry, 1974 (Box-folder 227: 11)
    - Jova, Joseph John, 1982 (Box-folder 227: 12)
    - Judd, Walter, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 227: 13)
    - Kearns International, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 227: 14)
    - Keating, Kenneth B., 1974-1975 (Box-folder 227: 15)
    - Kennedy, Dana, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 227: 16)
    - Kennedy, Moorhead, Jr., 1979-1981 (Box-folder 227: 17)
      Includes transcript of Kennedy's conversation with Reader's Digest relating to his captivity in Iran, 1979 November-1981 January.
    - Kimball, John, 1974-1981 (Box-folder 227: 18)
    - Kirkpatrick, Jeane, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 227: 19)
    - Kissinger, Henry, 1979 (Box-folder 227: 20)
    - Klein, Woody, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 227: 21)
    - Krebs, Max, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 227: 22)
    - Kriendler, John, 1982 (Box-folder 227: 23)
    - Krueger, Ernie, undated (Box-folder 227: 24)
    - Kubisch, Jack B., 1973 (Box-folder 227: 25)
    - Laird, Melvin, 1975 (Box-folder 227: 26)
    - Lamont, Mr. and Mrs. Gordon, 1974-1983 (Box-folder 227: 27)
    - Lane, Andrew, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 227: 28)
    - Langdon, Homer, 1975 (Box-folder 227: 29)
    - LaPorte-Cholet, 1982 (Box-folder 227: 30)
    - LaVarre, William, 1977 (Box-folder 227: 31)
    - Law, Marion, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 227: 32)
    - LeBaron, Robert, 1982 (Box-folder 227: 33)
    - Leboutillier, John, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 227: 34)
    - Leigh, Mrs. Douglas, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 227: 35)
    - Leone-Moats, Alice, 1977 (Box-folder 227: 36)
    - Levine, Laurence, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 227: 37)
    - Levy, Herman, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 227: 38)
    - Lichine, Alexis, 1977 (Box-folder 227: 39)
    - Llambi y Galvez, Carlos, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 227: 40)
    - Loder, John, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 227: 41)
    - Lodge, Francesca, 1975 (Box-folder 227: 42)
    - Lodge, George Cabot, Jr., 1976-1980 (Box-folder 227: 43)
    - Lodge, Henry Cabot, Jr., 1974-1982 (Box-folder 227: 44-45)
    - Loeb, William, 1974-1981 (Box-folder 228: 1)
    - Loomis, Pat, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 228: 2)
    - Lopez-Herce, Alberto, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 228: 3)
    - Loy, Thomas L., 1983 (Box-folder 228: 4)
    - Luce, Clare Boothe, 1983 (Box-folder 228: 5)
    - Lupton, John, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 228: 6)
    - MacArthur, Jean, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 228: 7)
    - Macaya, Ignacio, 1974-1981 (Box-folder 228: 8)
    - McCauley, Thurston, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 228: 9)
    - McClintock, Robert, 1976 (Box-folder 228: 10)
    - McEvoy, Joe, 1981 (Box-folder 228: 11)
    - McIlhenny, Henry P., 1974-1982 (Box-folder 228: 12)
    - McKeon, Daniel, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 228: 13)
    - McKinney, Stewart, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 228: 14)
    - Madariaga, Mr. and Mrs. Juan Jose de, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 228: 15)
    - Maione, Mike, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 228: 16)
    - Males, Liubimiro, 1973 (Box-folder 228: 17)
    - Mansfield, Mike, 1976 (Box-folder 228: 18)
    - Marcus, Lily (Lodge) and James, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 228: 19)
    - Marcus, Stanley, 1978 (Box-folder 228: 20)
    - Martin E. Janis and Company, 1974 (Box-folder 228: 21)
    - Martin Gamero, Adolfo, 1975 (Box-folder 228: 22)
    - Martin y Alonso-Martinez, Enrique, 1981 (Box-folder 228: 23)
    - Mason, Anne, 1974-1983 (Box-folder 228: 24)
    - Massachusetts Historical Society, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 228: 25)
    - Matz, Sally, 1977 (Box-folder 228: 26)
    - Maury, Reuben, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 228: 27)
    - Meek, Samuel, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 228: 28)
    - Meskill, Thomas, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 228: 29)
    - Mestre, Goar, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 228: 30)
    - Metcalfe, John H., 1975-1976 (Box-folder 228: 31)
    - Middlesex School, 1974 (Box-folder 228: 32)
    - Michel, Robert H., 1975-1982 (Box-folder 228: 33)
    - Middendorf, William, 1976-1983 (Box-folder 228: 34)
    - Misch, Robert, 1977 (Box-folder 229: 1)
    - Montllor, Joseph, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 229: 2)
    - Montgomery, Ruth B., 1982 (Box-folder 229: 3)
    - Moore, Frances, 1977 (Box-folder 229: 4)
    - Moore, Robin, 1974-1983 (Box-folder 229: 5)
    - Morison, Samuel Eliot, 1974 (Box-folder 229: 6)
    - Morris, Robert, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 229: 7)
    - Morton, Rogers C. B., 1976 (Box-folder 229: 8)
    - Mosher, Robert, 1975 (Box-folder 229: 9)
    - Mott, Jordan Manuel, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 229: 10)
    - Muinos, Alfredo, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 229: 11)
    - Muniz, Carlos Manuel, 1977 (Box-folder 229: 12)
    - Muns, Alejandro de, 1974-1983 (Box-folder 229: 13-14)
    - Murphy, George, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 229: 15)
    - Murphy, Robert, 1974 (Box-folder 229: 16)
    - Myer, Paul, 1976 (Box-folder 229: 17)
    - Napper, Bernice, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 229: 18)
    - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), 1975 (Box-folder 229: 19)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 229: 20)
    - National Strategy Information Center, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 229: 21)
    - National War College, 1974 (Box-folder 229: 22)
    - New York Times, 1978 (Box-folder 229: 23)
    - Nichols, William, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 229: 24)
    - Nixon, Richard M., 1973-1983 (Box-folder 229: 25)
    - Nofziger, Lyn, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 229: 26)
    - Norton, John, 1980 (Box-folder 229: 27)
    - Norton, Julian, 1974 (Box-folder 229: 28)
    - Norwalk Club, 1974 (Box-folder 229: 29)
    - Oakie, Mrs. Jack, 1982 (Box-folder 230: 1)
    - Oram, Frank, 1974-1983 (Box-folder 230: 2)
    - Orfila, Alejandro, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 230: 3)
    - Ortiz, Frank, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 230: 4)
    - Ortiz de Rozas, Carlos, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 230: 5)
    - Overton, Albert, 1974-1983 (Box-folder 230: 6-7)
    - Oyarzabal, Beatrice (Lodge) and Antonio de, 1974-1983 (Box-folder 230: 8-9)
    - Palm Beach Round Table, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 230: 10)
    - Pappas, Thomas A., 1975 (Box-folder 230: 11)
    - Parkinson, Mary Jane, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 230: 12)
    - Pasquaney Trust, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 230: 13)